&gt；&gt；steve kinney：酷，所以让我们试一试。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Cool, so
let's give it a shot and try it out.
我们要按下录音按钮
We're gonna hit the record button,
几次按双倍尺码，&gt；&gt；steve kinney：和
hit double sizes a few times,
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And
你可以看到我们这里有这些截图。
you can see we've got
these screenshots here.
我看到这些就像紫色的跳跃。
And I see these like jumps of purple.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：如果我们看，我们可以看到发生了什么。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: If we look
we can see what happens.
所以我们得到了click事件，调用一个函数，
So we've got the click event,
recalling a function,
我们马上来看一看。
we'll take a look at it in a second.
我们每个双倍宽度都有这个，
We've got this for
each double width but then,
真正的罪魁祸首在这里。
the real kind of culprit is down here.
当你看到一堆东西重复的时候，那不是很好。
When you see a bunch of stuff repeating,
that's not great.
如果你看，重新计算风格布局，
And if you look, recalculate style layout,
重新计算样式布局，一大堆时间。
recalculate style layout, recalculate
style layout, a whole bunch of times.
就像我们只是，我在这里做了一个序言说布局，不是很好。
Like we kind of just, I did a preamble
here saying layout, not great.
我的意思是，你可以看到这一帧花了48.7毫秒，
I mean, you can see this
frame took 48.7 milliseconds,
这远远超过了我们目标的16毫秒，对吧？
which is well past the 16 milliseconds
that we're aiming for, right?
这是每秒21帧，而不是60帧。
This was 21 frames a second, not 60.
对，所以因为我们在重新计算风格布局，
Right, so
because we are recalculating style layout,
重新计算风格布局如此之多，这通常是这里的罪魁祸首。
recalculating style layout so much,
that's usually where the big culprit here.
最后，我们甚至不得不在中间进行垃圾收集。
And then finally, we even had to do
a garbage collection in the middle there.
这就是浏览器前进的地方
That's where the browser goes ahead and
试图回收一些记忆来完成一些事情。
tries to reclaim some memory
to get some stuff done.
我们可以看看这个，我们知道我们有一个问题。
We can look at this,
we know that we have a problem.
最大的问题是我们的问题是什么，我们该怎么做？
The big question is what is our
problem and what do we do about it?
所以如果我们翻过来
So if we flip over and
看看代码，&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：我们
look at the code,
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: We
可以看出这是一段很漂亮的无伤大雅的代码，对吧，就像OK，就像GO
can see this is a pretty like innocuous
piece of code, right, like okay, like go
给我元素，用它们做一个数组，这样我就可以使用每个元素，因为我很懒。
get me the elements, make an array out of
them so I can use for each cuz I'm lazy.
只是宽度的两倍，对吧？
And just double their width, right?
但看起来我们遇到了一些问题。
But it seems like we've
got some kind of problem.
我可以尝试做的是改变一下这个代码。
What I could try to do is
kinda change this code.
因此，我可能会考虑如何重构它。
So here's how I might
consider refactoring it.
在这里，我会继续
In here, I will go ahead and
我先看看能不能算出它们的宽度。
I'm gonna see if I can figure out
the widths of all of them first.
我会先计算出所有的宽度，然后我会更新所有的宽度。
I'm gonna figure out all the widths first
and then I'm going to update all of them.
我们看看会不会有什么效果。
We'll see if that has any effect.
让我在一秒钟内去掉这个双倍宽的行，但是让我们继续
Let me get rid of this double width row
in a second, but let's go ahead and
让我们，它甚至会在技术上更多的代码，对吧，每个人都像是不要循环通过
lets, it'll even be technically more code,
right, everyone is like don't loop through
东西两次，那是浪费，你知道吗，我不需要别人告诉我怎么做。
stuff twice, that's a waste you know what,
I don't need to be told what to do.
我们会继续，我们会拿到盒子，然后
And we'll go ahead and
we'll get the boxes, and
像所有的老板一样，盒子，我们会在它们上面绘制地图，然后继续
like all the bosses, the boxes and
we'll map over them and like go ahead and
给我一个所有宽度的数组。
get me an array of all of the widths.
让我们先把它弄开，这样我们就可以看到了，
Let's get that out of way first,
so we can see,
所以酷给我一个事件的集合。
so cool give me an event of set with.
不管我教和教编程有多少年了，
Despite how many years I've been
teaching and teaching programming,
当人们看着我的时候，我仍然不能正确地打字，而且
I still can't type correctly when
people are looking at me, and
它永远不会改变，所以我在这里。
it's never gonna change so here I am.
那么我们将检查所有的盒子，&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：我们将
So then we'll go through all the boxes,
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And we'll for
每一个都超过了他们。
each over them.
对于每个实际上需要两个参数。
And for each actually takes two arguments.
它会接受你要迭代的东西，它实际上需要三个参数。
It'll take the thing you're iterating over
and it actually takes three arguments.
它还将采用它当前所在的索引。
It'll also take the index
that it's currently on.
所以，零，一，二，三，四，直到它结束。
So, zero, one, two, three,
four, until it gets to the end.
我想，我应该告诉你第三件事是什么，因为我提到了需要三个
I guess, I should tell you what the third
thing is since I mentioned it takes three
这并不重要。
and it's not important.
第三个参数是整个数组本身。
Is the third argument is
the entire array itself.
所以盒子排成了一排。
So the boxes array.
如果有人对它为什么要这样做有任何疑问，我不知道。
If anyone has questions on why
does it do that, I don't know.
所以，我们拿到了盒子，我们仔细检查了每个盒子
So, we got the boxes,
we go through each of them and
然后我们会说元素点样式点宽度。
then we'll say element
dot style dot width.
我们会继续，我们会说，无论你在阵列中的什么地方，都去吧。
And we'll go ahead and we'll say go
get wherever you were in the array.
乘以2。
Multiply that by two.
然后设置成这样。
And set it like that.
&gt；&gt；演讲者2：你的意思是把箱子放到第十行添加吗？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Did you mean
boxes down to add on line ten?
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：是的，我可能太忙于思考我将如何
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Yep, I was probably
too busy thinking of how I was gonna
做一个评论，我不能在人们面前打字，这是我自己造成的问题。
make a comment that I can't type in front
of people and caused that problem myself.
好吧，那我们去看看吧。
All right, so let's go check it out.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：我们会继续前进，我们会打开我们的工具，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: We'll go ahead,
we'll open up our tools,
我们再录一遍。
let's do another recording.
我没有被定义，让我们去解决这个问题。
I is not defined, let's go fix that.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：在此期间停止录制。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Stop
the recording while we do that.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：把这两个地方都称为索引。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Call
it index both places.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：回到整个页面，是的，留下来保存。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Go back to the full page,
yeah, stay and save.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：好的，我们现在再试一次。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: All right,
let's try it again now.
去吧，我们会录下来的。
Go ahead and we'll record.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：如果我们看一看，我们可以看到，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And
if we take a look, we can see,
让我们找到他们第一个双倍的地方。
let's find the place
where they first double.
去吧，放大一下。
Go, kinda zoom in there.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：而且发生的事情少了很多。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And
there's a lot less happening.
整个事情发生了，即使我现在把所有的东西都循环了两次，
The whole thing happens even though
I'm looping over everything twice now,
整个事情发生在13.2毫秒左右，对吧，
the whole thing happens in
about 13.2 milliseconds, right,
好像少了很多。
like that's a lot less.
你可以看到最重要的部分是我没有所有的紫色
And you can see the most important part
is I don't have all of those purple
小酒吧，不像为什么这么快？
little bars, not like why is this fast?
因为我做的事情比较少，对吧，我没有反复检查这件事
Because I did less stuff, right, I didn't
do this thing repeatedly of checking
布局，重新计算样式，检查布局，重新计算样式。
layout, recalculating style,
checking layout, recalculating style.
我的代码唯一的大不同是，不是逐个检查
The only big difference with my code is
that instead of checking each one for
它的宽度，然后调整它，我先得到所有的宽度，
its width and then adjusting it,
I got all the widths first and
然后我调整了所有的宽度。
then I adjusted all the widths.
好的，有没有人记得我有一张大幻灯片，上面有所有的原因和
All right, does anyone remember that large
slide I had with all the reasons and
其中一个是计算风格，对，引起回流。
one of them was calculating the styles,
right, causes a reflow.
喜欢的简单行为，试图找出某物的大小
The simple act of like,
trying to figure out the size of something
使浏览器重排页面，因此
causes the browser to reflow the page,
and so
我通过检查，更新，检查，更新来支付这个费用。
I was paying that cost by checking,
updating, checking, updating.
所以让我们更多地谈谈那里发生的事情。
So let's talk a little more
about what's going on there.